<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wherwell</title>
    <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Wherwell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Wherwell v Hursley Park (home, 12/06/2021)</title>
      <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2021/wherwell-v-hursley-park-2s-12-06-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2021/wherwell-v-hursley-park-2s-12-06-2021/</guid>
      <description>We clawed, we chained, our hearts in vain, We jumped, never asking why We kissed, I fell under your spell, A love no one could deny Don&amp;rsquo;t you ever say I just walked away, I will always want you I can&amp;rsquo;t live a lie, running for my life, I will always want you
Chasing 185, Hursley were 157-4… Wherwell came in like a wrecking ball Having won the toss Wherwell elected to bat, the pitch looked good and the weather better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chawton v Wherwell (away, 05/06/2021)</title>
      <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2021/chawton-v-wherwell-05-06-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2021/chawton-v-wherwell-05-06-2021/</guid>
      <description>When you&amp;rsquo;re weary, Feeling small When tears are in your eyes, I&amp;rsquo;ll dry them all I&amp;rsquo;m on your side, Oh, when times get rough And friends just can&amp;rsquo;t be found
Troubled waters at camp Wherwell after yesterday&amp;rsquo;s result, but the bridge is that we’ve been here before. In 2019 we suffered an early defeat at the hands of Chawton and went on to win the league.. history has a habit of repeating itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wherwell v Hartley Wintney (home, 29/05/2021)</title>
      <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2021/wherwell-v-hartley-wintney-home-29-05-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2021/wherwell-v-hartley-wintney-home-29-05-2021/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been twenty hours and 638 days since they took league cricket away And nothing compares
Wherwell have been itching to get their inaugural Div 3 campaign underway having been hampered by inclement weather throughout May. With the month almost gone without a ball bowled in anger, the forecasts suggested that league cricket would once again commence.
Wherwell won the toss and having chosen to bat were stunned to be 3-1 after the first over, Cooke (2) failing on debut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Membership Form 2021</title>
      <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/posts/2021/membership-form-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/posts/2021/membership-form-2021/</guid>
      <description>Complete the below form to become a member!
We offer three simple tiers: silver, full-time student and casual.
Silver costs £180 p/year or £15.00 p/month:
 Includes cost for sign up and match fees for all league matches. New members will receive free trousers and shirt  Full-time students is £10 sign up cost and all match fees are £4 per game.
Casual membership is simply £1 sign up cost and all match fees are £10 per game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wherwell v East Woodhay (home, 22/08/2020)</title>
      <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2020/wherwell-v-east-woodhay-home-22-08-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2020/wherwell-v-east-woodhay-home-22-08-2020/</guid>
      <description>A lump of coal is turned into a diamond with relentless pressure, and that’s exactly what Wherwell exerted against East Woodhay. Top bowling and tight fielding giving very little opportunity.
However it started with a gift, a loopy full toss loosener from Emslie’s first ball was miscued to midwicket, the apology offered probably didn’t make the batsman feel any better. Emslie struck again finding some seam movement and both openers were gone early before a short rain break came.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
