<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1streports2017 on Wherwell</title>
    <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/categories/1streports2017/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1streports2017 on Wherwell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wherwellcc.co.uk/categories/1streports2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Old Basing II v Wherwell (away, 26/08/2017)</title>
      <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2017/old-basing-ii-v-wherwell-away-26082017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2017/old-basing-ii-v-wherwell-away-26082017/</guid>
      <description>KJM Group Ltd sponsored Wherwell were away to Old Basing II for the last game of the season. Skipper S Taylor won the toss for the 2nd time this season and Wherwell elected to bat first.
The top order showed good composer with notable scores Stuart Taylor (81), putting Wherwell in a comfortable position cemented further by Alex Gladwyn’s (46) steady knock. Runs trickled through as wickets were slowly picked off by Old Basing II, walking off with 236 for 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wherwell v Ramsdell (home, 19/08/2017)</title>
      <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2017/wherwell-v-ramsdell-home-19082017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2017/wherwell-v-ramsdell-home-19082017/</guid>
      <description>KJM sponsored Wherwell played at home against promotion rivals Ramsdell in a crucial match that would decide either teams’ chances of going up this season. S Taylor lost his 11th toss for the season and was put out to bat on a mildy damp wicket.
Ramsdell had an impressive bowling attack with a double wicket maiden in the 6th over having Wherwell on the back foot. R Skeates showed patience early on but wickets tumbled through Wherwell’s usually dominant batting order leaving R Chetwynd-Talbot top scorer with 11.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St Cross IV v Wherwell (away, 12/08/2017)</title>
      <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2017/st-cross-iv-v-wherwell-away-12082017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2017/st-cross-iv-v-wherwell-away-12082017/</guid>
      <description>KJM sponsored Wherwell played at St Cross on a gloomy day and skipper S Taylor lost the toss again and was put out to bat on a mildly damp wicket.
Incredible performances by the top order kept Wherwell flying high gunning for promotion. R Skeates and G Elwes gave Wherwell the steady start they needed, but after 15o R Skeates had enough and started pummelling. Whippersnapper Elwes enabled the top order and handed the baton to S Taylor who quickly picked up 104 peaking the run rate above 10 at one point before being bowled but leaving his side in a strong position of 237 for 2 off 27.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wherwell v Medstead (home, 05/08/2017)</title>
      <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2017/wherwell-v-medstead-home-05082017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2017/wherwell-v-medstead-home-05082017/</guid>
      <description>Stuart Taylor lost another toss and were put into bat on a two-paced wicket. The Wherwell batsmen definitely got their cardio workout due to the slow outfield. All the batsmen got starts however no one was able to fully capitalise on their start. Robbie Skeates top scored with 32 runs, Nathan Young scored 24 runs and Harry Trebert scored 23 runs. R Simpson took 4 wickets for Medstead to keep Wherwell&amp;rsquo;s innings in check.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wherwell v Alton III (home, 15/07/2017)</title>
      <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2017/wherwell-v-alton-iii-home-15072017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2017/wherwell-v-alton-iii-home-15072017/</guid>
      <description>Wherwell played at home against Alton III&amp;rsquo;s and skipper S Taylor lost the toss and was told to bat.
Wherwell&amp;rsquo;s batting gave Alton a strong reply to their choice to bowl first. R Skeates (17, lbw), S Taylor (60, ct), R Chetwynd-Talbot (20, runout), O Emslie (31, bowled) and J Trebertt (17, not out). Alton III&amp;rsquo;s gave 29 extras to Wherwell giving the home team a reasonable 201 to defend. M Guilfoyle was the only batsmen to not score runs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
