<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1streports2014 on Wherwell</title>
    <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/categories/1streports2014/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1streports2014 on Wherwell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/categories/1streports2014/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alton III v Wherwell (away, 23/08/2014)</title>
      <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/alton-iii-v-wherwell-away-23082014/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/alton-iii-v-wherwell-away-23082014/</guid>
      <description>Wherwell 1st X1&amp;rsquo;s skipper, Craig Beckingham, won the toss and decided to bowl first on a green pitch with overcast conditions.
The first innings ticked along nicely for Wherwell with tremendous pressure on Alton where they were just 25 runs off 10 overs. However, with such consistency from both sides, Oliver Emslie went for 21 off 7 overs for 0 and Craig Beckingham at 25 off 7 overs for 2 wickets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wherwell v AWE Tadley (home, 16/08/2014)</title>
      <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-awetadley-home-16082014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-awetadley-home-16082014/</guid>
      <description>Wherwell won the toss, pitch was green, weather was English. Skipper decided to bowl first on their own strip.
A rare occasion for Wherwell 1st XI playing with just 10 men occured against AWE Tadley. However the hard work was contributed with great team spirit as always regardless of the situation, where Matt Guilfoyle bowled 24 runs off 10 overs for 3 wickets, Craig Beckingham making it difficult for AWE Tadley with just 15 runs off 7 overs, and finally Ed Marsh with 28 runs off 6 overs for 3 wickets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM Hursley v Wherwell (away, 09/08/2014)</title>
      <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/ibm-hursley-v-wherwell-away-09082014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/ibm-hursley-v-wherwell-away-09082014/</guid>
      <description>KJM sponsored travelled to Hursley with a weakened team but full of energy and knowing they should just enjoy the day regardless of result.
After losing the toss they were asked to bat on a very green strip. After losing a few early wickets, Alex Gladwyn and Matt Guilfoyle tried to rebuild the innings with some smart running. Wherwell started to rebuild until a rush of blood was the downfall of Guilfoyle as he played all around a straight ball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wherwell v Andover 3rds (home, 02/08/2014)</title>
      <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-andover-3rds-home-02082014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-andover-3rds-home-02082014/</guid>
      <description>KJM sponsored Wherwell took on Andover 3rds trying to turn around a recent run of defeats. After winning the toss Wherwell decided to bat knowing the weather was going to play a part. After only 3 over the players rushed of the pitch due to a heavy downpour. Exactly 60 minutes and after some hard work the ground was deemed playable. Wherwell lost 3 quick wickets as the pitch was damp on top and Robin Richards 5-12 from 9 overs exposed the uncovered pitch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hobos v Wherwell (away, 26/07/2014)</title>
      <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/hobos-v-wherwell-away-26072014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/hobos-v-wherwell-away-26072014/</guid>
      <description>KJM sponsored Wherwell travelled east towards to Basingstoke for what has become a familiar trip (having played away 3 years running to Hobos). After losing the Wherwell were asked to field on probably the hottest Saturday of the year, as the bowlers rotated in the heat Wherwell struggled with the conditions as a few errors crept in. They did however get a injection of energy at second drinks as they started chipping away at the wickets wit regular success.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
