<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1streports2015 on Wherwell</title>
    <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/categories/1streports2015/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1streports2015 on Wherwell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wherwellcc.co.uk/categories/1streports2015/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bishops Waltham v Wherwell (away, 22/08/2015)</title>
      <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2015/bishops-waltham-vs-wherwell-away-22082015/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2015/bishops-waltham-vs-wherwell-away-22082015/</guid>
      <description>Wherwell made the journey to Promotion chasing Bishops Waltham on a gloriously sunny summers day knowing that the chance of promotion had likely slipped by for another year but still with plenty of positives to play for.
Skipper for the day, Alex Gladwyn, won the toss and elected to bowl first under the clear skies on what looked to be a cracking strip much to the bemusement of his team. However once the opening bowlers got loose it proved an inspired decision both Emslie and Taylor bowled with great control and were backed up in the field with Charlie Ingrem in particular excelling at cover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oakley vs Wherwell (away, 18/07/2015)</title>
      <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2015/oakley-vs-wherwell-away-18072015/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2015/oakley-vs-wherwell-away-18072015/</guid>
      <description>KJM sponsored Wherwell travelled to Oakley for the first time in a few years. After winning the toss Skipper Nathan Young thought it would be a good idea to bowl on a slightly green track. The pitch however offered very little to the bowlers. Skipper Young and Oliver Emslie opened the bowling with no success, a few bowling changes followed though as Wherwell searched for a breakthrough. Oakley openers Dique 92 and Summer 54 put on a magnificent 133 run partnership as they made Wherwell work very hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wherwell v Colden Common (home, 04/07/2015)</title>
      <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2015/wherwell-v-colden-common-home-04072015/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2015/wherwell-v-colden-common-home-04072015/</guid>
      <description>KJM sponsored Wherwell hosted Colden Common on what was probably the hottest Saturday of the year. Wherwell lost the toss and were asked to bat. Wherwell started with serious intent as Robbie Skeates 52 and Craig Beckingham 40 put on a impressive 80 runs partnership from the first 15 overs, They both fell within a few overs of each other as Alex Gladwyn 58 and Stuart Taylor 93 carried on the impressive scoring as they shared a 100 run partnership.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
