<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1streports2012 on Wherwell</title>
    <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/categories/1streports2012/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1streports2012 on Wherwell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/categories/1streports2012/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Andover 3rd XI v Wherwell (away, 18/08/2012)</title>
      <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/andover-3rd-xi-v-wherwell-18082012-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/andover-3rd-xi-v-wherwell-18082012-away/</guid>
      <description>Both teams went into the game knowing it was going to be a real close one. KJM sponsored Wherwell in true tradition lost the toss and were asked to bat. Craig Beckingham and Stuart Taylor opened the batting and faced a some good lines and lengths from Robin Richards and Robbie Taylor. A smart catch by Stewart Clackson seen the end of Craig Beckingham, Taylor got a lifeline when bowled from a no-ball, he would go one to punish the bowlers for this mistake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wherwell v Sparsholt 2nd XI (home, played @ Hurstebourne,  25/08/2012)</title>
      <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-sparsholt-2nd-xi-25082012-home-played-at-hurstbourne/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-sparsholt-2nd-xi-25082012-home-played-at-hurstbourne/</guid>
      <description>1st XI sign off with Thunder and Lightening.
Aptly for this summer Wherwell were forced to play a home game on a neighbours ground under leaden skies with rain forecast. Whilst many games were called off Wherwell debated how to get the mower going so that the pitch would be more suitable for cricket rather than a picnic, unfortunately whilst they pondered this the unthinkable happened, Captain Dave Langford won the toss!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whitchurch vs Wherwell (away, 11/08/2012)</title>
      <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/whitchurch-vs-wherwell-11082012-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/whitchurch-vs-wherwell-11082012-away/</guid>
      <description>KJM sponsored Wherwell travelled the short distance over to Whitchurch in a must win game to keep survival hopes alive. Both teams hampered with injuries and holidays did well to field to 11 players. Wherwell lost the toss and were asked to bat, Wherwell got lucky in the first over when Taylor was dropped from his first ball, something Whitchurch would go on to regret. Leamon fell early at the other end to a well taken catch.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
