<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>friendlyreports2014 on Wherwell</title>
    <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/categories/friendlyreports2014/</link>
    <description>Recent content in friendlyreports2014 on Wherwell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wherwellcc.co.uk/categories/friendlyreports2014/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crawley v Wherwell (away, 17/08/2014)</title>
      <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/crawley-v-wherwell-away-17082014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/crawley-v-wherwell-away-17082014/</guid>
      <description>Wherwell travelled to Crawley in an entertaining fixture, which was fitting for Crawley in their centenary season. Wherwell won the toss and elected to bat. After the fall of 2 early wickets, opener Ed John and Stuart Taylor made good starts before getting out, short of their half centuries. Wherwell maintained a healthy run rate, but wickets continued to fall. With 180 looking a par score, Wherwell struggled on 141-6. However, that brought the partnership of Charles Ingreme and Luke Trebert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wherwell v Sway (home, 10/08/2014)</title>
      <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-sway-home-10082014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-sway-home-10082014/</guid>
      <description>After an unpredictable evening before the game of weather and some hard work from several Wherwell players, the pitch was deemed playable and the call was made to Sway to travel up.
Wherwell&amp;rsquo;s Sunday skipper won the toss and chose to bat on a damp looking pitch. Openers Stuart Taylor and Jordan Trebert opened the batting and were greeted with some very generous bowling, of which Taylor made the most of it, by reaching his 50 just after 3 overs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wherwell v Southampton Warriors (home, 27/08/2014)</title>
      <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-southampton-warriors-home-27082014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-southampton-warriors-home-27082014/</guid>
      <description>KJM sponsored wherwell looked to get back to winning ways in there Sunday friendly against Southampton warriors. Captain Alex Gladwyn won the toss and decided to bat first. Wherwell lost early wickets and after 8 overs were 27 for 3, this brought together inform Stuart Taylor and captain Gladwyn, both batsman batted well and put together an 85 run partnership before Gladwyn departed for 36. Taylor held the innings together striking some lusty blows before being bowled for 96 trying to smash his way to his 5th 100 this season but got Wherwell to good total of 224.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
