<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1st-xi-reports-2021 on Wherwell</title>
    <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/categories/1st-xi-reports-2021/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1st-xi-reports-2021 on Wherwell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wherwellcc.co.uk/categories/1st-xi-reports-2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rasmdell  v Wherwell (away, 17/07/2021)</title>
      <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2021/ramsdell-v-wherwell-17-07-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2021/ramsdell-v-wherwell-17-07-2021/</guid>
      <description>My heroes had the heart to lose their lives out on the limb And all I remember is thinking I want to be like them Ever since I was little Ever since I was little it looked like fun And it&amp;rsquo;s no coincidence I&amp;rsquo;ve come And I can die when I&amp;rsquo;m done Crazy- Gnarls Barkley
Our regular wordsmith believes that a kite before the the game is good luck, goodness knows what he would have made of 7 of the beasts flying high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wherwell v RAM (home, 10/07/2021)</title>
      <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2021/wherwell-v-ram-10-07-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2021/wherwell-v-ram-10-07-2021/</guid>
      <description>I let it fall, my heart, And as it fell, you rose to claim it It was dark and I was over, Until you kissed my lips and you saved me My hands, they were strong, But my knees were far too weak To stand in your arms, Without falling to your feet But there&amp;rsquo;s a side to you, That I never knew, never knew All the things you&amp;rsquo;d say, They were never true, never true And the games you&amp;rsquo;d play, You would always win, always win Set Fire to the Rain ~ Adele</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Farley v Wherwell (away, 03/07/2021)</title>
      <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2021/farley-v-wherwell-03-07-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2021/farley-v-wherwell-03-07-2021/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a street walking cheetah with a heart full of napalm, I&amp;rsquo;m a runaway son of the nuclear A-bomb I am a world&amp;rsquo;s forgotten boy, The one who searches and destroys Honey, gotta help me please, Somebody gotta save my soul, Baby, detonate for me, aw! Look out honey, &amp;lsquo;cause I&amp;rsquo;m using technology, Ain&amp;rsquo;t got time to make no apology
The weather looked questionable. The pitch looked decent. The ground looked in good nick if a little short one side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wherwell v Liss (home, 26/06/2021)</title>
      <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2021/wherwell-v-liss-26-06-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2021/wherwell-v-liss-26-06-2021/</guid>
      <description>On the first part of the journey, I was looking at all the life There were plants and birds and rocks and things, There was sand and hills and rings The first thing I met was a fly with a buzz, And the sky with no clouds The heat was hot, and the ground was dry, But the air was full of sound I&amp;rsquo;ve been through the desert…
No one likes to see a club struggling for numbers, especially one established in 1880, so all credit to Liss for turning up to honour the fixture even though they had to start with 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ropley v Wherwell (away, 19/06/2021)</title>
      <link>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2021/ropley-v-wherwell-19-06-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2021/ropley-v-wherwell-19-06-2021/</guid>
      <description>Livin&#39; room, Passin&#39; time, Talkin&#39; trash, Sippin&#39; wine I need somethin&#39; more substantial!
New deck, Playin&#39; cards, I don&amp;rsquo;t like to work this hard I think I&amp;rsquo;ll have to cancel!
I&amp;rsquo;m runnin&#39; outta time, About to lose my mind I got the six, Gimme your nine!
The Wherwell wrecking ball is picking up momentum with a comprehensive victory over Ropley this week. Despite the size of the victory there are still some areas for improvement and that means we can only get better!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
