<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1streports2013 on Wherwell</title>
    <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/categories/1streports2013/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1streports2013 on Wherwell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/categories/1streports2013/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Andover 3rd XI v Wherwell (away, 03/08/2013)</title>
      <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-andover-3rd-xi-away-03082013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-andover-3rd-xi-away-03082013/</guid>
      <description>KJM sponsored made the short journey to London Road 2 pitch, to find a wicket that looked dull and lifeless, After winning the toss Wherwell inserted their hosts and with no real back bone to their innings Andover soon collapsed away as Wherwell took wickets at regular intervals bowled out there hosts for just 117, with the pick of bowlers Mark Pettman 3-25, Stuart Taylor 2-15 and Matt Guilfoyle 2-20.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compton &amp; CF v Wherwell (away, 25/05/2013)</title>
      <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-compton-cf-away-25052013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-compton-cf-away-25052013/</guid>
      <description>With summer finally making a show KJM sponsored Wherwell 1st XI travelled to play Compton &amp;amp; Chandlers Ford, the ground looking perfect set as it is amongst a private development and benefitting from significant recent investments in it&amp;rsquo;s infrastructure that provided excellent protection from the previous days rain. With Captain &amp;ldquo;Trucker&amp;rdquo; Taylor winning the toss he typically elected to bat first.
Unfortunately the plan didn&amp;rsquo;t pan out as hoped with both Wherwell openers falling in single figures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hobos v Wherwell (away, 20/07/2013)</title>
      <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-hobos-away-20072013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-hobos-away-20072013/</guid>
      <description>KJM Sponsored Wherwell made the trip to Hobos just outside of Basingstoke, in an unlikely turn of events captain Stuart Taylor won the toss and for a change Wherwell chose to bowl first on a very average looking strip. This decision soon proved to be vindicated with the Wherwell bowlers taking regular wickets. The visiting side bowled Hobos out inside 21 overs for just 57. Nathan Young 3 for 4, Christian Nicel 3 for 12, Matt Guilfoyle 3 for 14 and Stuart Taylor 1-15 picking up all the wickets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Midhurst 2nd XI v Wherwell (away, 15/06/2013)</title>
      <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-midhurst-2nd-xi-away-15062013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-midhurst-2nd-xi-away-15062013/</guid>
      <description>KJM sponsored Wherwell 1st XI travelled to Midhurst in West Sussex. Wherwell won the toss and bowled first. Midhurst scored 139 all out on a damp surface, S Lush top scoring with 66. Stuart Taylor 3-30 Matt Guilfoyle 3-21 Nathan Young 2 -22 Christian Nicel 1-14 were the wicket takers. In reply Stuart Taylor 11 Nathan Young 30 opened the batting getting Wherwell off to a good start with contributions from Elton Adamo 21 Alex Gladwyn 35no Dave Langford 15 and Matt Guilfoyle 11no saw Wherwell comfortably home to the total and ending up on 140-4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petersfield v Wherwell 1st XI (away, 06/07/2013)</title>
      <link>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-petersfield-1st-xi-away-06072013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.wherwellcc.co.uk/reports/2014/wherwell-v-petersfield-1st-xi-away-06072013/</guid>
      <description>KJM sponsored Wherwell always knew this trip would be a tough one and so it proved under the blazing sun they were asked to bat first on what looked a good track. Taylor and John started well but both fell as the pitch showed some variable pace and bounce. Once again indiscipline showed as the middle order got them selves out with a combination of poor shot choice and bad luck.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
